arcadepod.com 2019-05-12

# ArcadePod.Com: Free Online Games

**ArcadePod.Com Privacy Policy** (updated as of 09/10/2009)

* * *

ArcadePod.Com, its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information. 

**Acceptance of Terms**

Please read this policy carefully since by visiting this website (“Website”) and/or sharing information with us, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy may be revised or updated at any time by us. This page was last updated as of the date at the top of this Privacy Policy. 

**Consumer Information**

During the process of delivering an ad to you, no personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address is collected. However, some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example) are obtained. The information collected are used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers. 

In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific ad (this ad may ask you to fill out a survey or provide your zip code). If this does occur, this information may be collected on behalf of an advertiser. This information is used by an advertiser to respond to your request. In addition, This information may be combined with other users' information and review it in an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who view a specific type of ad or visit a particular kind of website. 

**Data Collection and Opt Out**

Ads shown on our site, as well as most sites on the Internet, use "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. These cookies cannot be used to personally identify you in any way. What are cookies and why do we use them? A cookie is a unique number that is provided to you the first time an ad is served to you. This unique number, which is stored in a cookie file on your computer, helps target ads to you. This cookie can help ensure that the same ad will not be served you multiple times, and help our advertisers understand what you like and don't like about their offerings so that they can cater better to your needs the next time you are interested in their products or services. While we believe that cookies enhance your Internet experience by limiting the number of times you see the same ad and delivering more relevant content to you, they are not required for an ad to be delivered you. 

If you do not want the benefit of cookies, there is a simple procedure to manually delete your cookies. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information. A useful resource on understanding Cookies may be found at [allaboutcookies.org](http://allaboutcookies.org/). 

**Changes**

As the standards governing Internet privacy continue to evolve, ArcadePod.com may find it appropriate or necessary to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. As a result, we reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time and shall post such changes on the Website. Our Website will state the date the Privacy Policy was last updated. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you use this Website to make sure you understand how your information will be used. If we materially change how we use your Information, we will notify via a prominent notice on the Website prior to implementing the change. 

If you have any additional questions about ArcadePod.Com's dedication to consumer privacy, please contact us at [webmaster@arcadepod.com](mailto:webmaster@arcadepod.com). 

* * *

This site, ArcadePod.Com, uses the services of ValueClick, Casale Media and Google Ads for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, they collects anonymous data through the use of cookies. 

To learn more about ValueClick, please visit <http://www.valueclickmedia.com/webuser_privacy.shtml>. 

ValueClick Media is a member of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). The NAI is a cooperative of online marketing and analytics companies committed to building consumer awareness and establishing responsible business and data management practices and standards. For more information, please visit [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

* * *
